HOSSAM SHARAF

Site and Technical Office Engineer

CONTACT

•Name: Hossam-Eddin Nasser Ramadan Sharaf-Eddin

• Nationality: Egyptian

• Date of Birth: 12 of May 1998

• Place of Birth: El Mansoura

Marital Status: Single

• Email Address:

hossamnasser12359@gmai,.com

• Phone number: 011 0250 79 88

SKILLS

- Project Management
- Leadership and management.
- Problem solving.
- Ensure that health and safety policies are obeyed.
- Excellent communication skills.
- Active learner.

PROGRAMS

- Primavera P6
- EXCEL
- Cutting optimization
- Auto CAD
- REVIT
- SketchUp
- Blender 3d
- Lumion Render

LANGUAGES

- Arabic (Mother tongue)
- English (good)

ABOUT ME

Fresh Q.S engineer with more than 6 months of experience in sites and residential buildings, Strong drive to succeed with an exceptional aptitude for identifying risks and developing solutions. Ability to work alone or with a team. Proven leadership skills include being detail-oriented and managing time wisely.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Civil Engineering

2016-2021 Building and Construction Engineering (BCE) - Mansoura

University - Credit Hours

GPA: 3 of 4 points (very good)

Graduation project: The Effect of Magnetic Water on concrete

on Properties of Concrete

4 of 4 points (GPA)

Gamasa

WORK EXPERIENCE HISTORY:

Site Engineer, Petroblaaim company

2018

 Developed strong project management, site work and leadership while assisting in many constructions where 15 villas were built for the engineers working for the company.

Site Engineer, Arab constructors company

Mansoura

2019-2020

• Training in establishing residential buildings in Mansoura

*Also I ve helped my teammates in a full graduation planning project

Under supervision **Dr. Emad El Beltagy**, and managed to get A+.

· Design some residential buildings, Modeling And rendering as a

freelancer.

Mansoura

2019-2020